Just like happy, our good things can change us, bad things can too.
Touching a hot stove and getting burned teaches us to stay away from it.
Playing a boring game helps us learn not to play it again.
Sometimes people fight with family or friends, and that can really change how we feel.
It's good to learn from bad things so we don't make the same mistakes again,
but sometimes too many bad things can start to change the way we think and feel.
For example, if you burn your hand, you'll probably be more careful around the stove
and stay back when it's hot.
That's smart, but if you always stay away from the stove,
it might be hard to cook when you're older and have to make your own food.
That's how bad things can affect us.
At first, we do things to keep ourselves safe, but later, those things might not help us anymore.